https://www.gremlin-bells.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

.
All American - 27 Mill St - Johnston, RI 02919 - CONTACT USAll of our products are made in the USA and are available for wholesale.
Over 30 Years Experience...Manufacturing Lead-Free Pewter Gremlin Bells®,Motorcycle Biker Pins, Vest Extenders and more... gbells.com
Items in Cart: 0  Total: $0.00
Our Gremlin bells act as a guardian against all sorts of unwanted occurrences.If you're a biker, you'll love to ride with these bells. Fantastic gifts for bikers of all breeds!
Home
Our Newest Items
Search
Products
Gremlin Bells®
Pin Keepers
Vest Extenders
Biker Pins
Guardian Angel Gremlin Bell
Eagle with Upturned Wings Gremlin...
Live to Ride Gremlin Bell
Colored American Flag Gremlin Bell
Lady Rider Gremlin Bell
Colored Rebel Flag Gremlin Bell
Marine (USMC) Gremlin Bell
Army Gremlin Bell
Flame Gremlin Bell
Celtic Cross Gremlin Bell
St. Christopher Gremlin Bell
Skull & Crossbones Gremlin Bell
Firefighter Gremlin Bell
Biker Chick Gremlin Bell
POW Gremlin Bell
US Navy Gremlin Bell
Breast Cancer Awareness Gremlin...
Flying Wheel Gremlin Bell
Support our Troops Gremlin Bell
Gold Wing Gremlin Bell
USA Cross Gremlin Bell
Motorcycle Angel Gremlin Bell
Ride It Like You Stole It Gremlin...
Indian Head Nickel Gremlin Bell
Police Gremlin Bell
Brotherhood Gremlin Bell
Support Our Troops Gremlin Bell
V-Twin Gremlin Bell
Privacy Notice
All American
is committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we
have adopted this Privacy Policy. It is intended to describe how we use and
process your personal information. Please note that by visiting and using All
American
website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy
Policy.
What information is All American gathering about its visitors
and how is it being used?
Every computer connected to the Internet is provided with a domain name (e.g.
cox.net) and an IP address (e.g. 68.122.1.100). When a visitor requests a page
from within the All American
website, our web servers automatically
identify and log the HTTP request that is made to them, as follows:
The IP address of the site that may have referred you.
Your IP address.
The web page from which you linked to us.
The product identifier for version and make of browser (e.g. Internet
Explorer 7.0).
The operating system that you are running (e.g. Mac OS, Windows, Linux).
Search words or terms that are passed from a search engine (e.g. Google,
Yahoo, or Lycos).
There is nothing unusual, in our view, about the information just described,
and the practice of collecting this data has been generally standardized by many
web servers today.
The purpose of this information is actually two-fold. One, All
American
has found it advantageous to examine visitor traffic in its aggregate so that we
can ensure maximum compatibility for the various browsers and operating systems
that visit our site. By analyzing these and other visitation patterns, referring
URLs and search engine terms, we can strategically enhance our exposure on the
Internet.
What about cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are transferred to your computer's hard
drive through your web browser from our web server. All American
website
uses cookies in some situations as a means of providing personalization features
to our visitors. For example, we use cookies to remember personal settings that
you may have chosen at our website.
You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings of
your browser. Typically, by accessing the browsers help feature you can obtain
information on how to prevent your browser from accepting all cookies or to
notify you when a cookie is being set. If you choose no to accept these cookies,
your experience at our website and other websites may be diminished and some
features may not work as intended.
What other information does All American request?
We may also request your email address or mailing address for the purposes of
conducting a survey, adding you to our mailing list, or by your request to have
someone contact you for additional information. Whenever we request the identity
of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the
information is requested. We will not sell, rent, or otherwise give your email
address to a third party.
Will All American
website disclose the information collected to third
parties?
All American
website will disclose your personal information or any of its
log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such
actions are necessary to:
Confirm the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on All
American
website.
Protect and defend the rights or property of All American
website, or
visitors of All American
website.
Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the
rights of third parties. Cooperate with the investigations of purported
unlawful activities.
Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page.
Home | Shipping Info | Privacy Notice | Custom Event Pins & Patches
Shipping Info
About us
Contact us
Wholesale Info
New Items
Satisfaction Guaranteed
Links
Track Order
gbells.com - Copyright © 2020 All American Gremlin Bells®. Gremlin Bell® is a US Registered ® Trademark - Registration Number 2,920,388 - S/N 76517074
Parse Time: 2.738 - Number of Queries: 93 - Query Time: 0.063378151351929
SSL
